Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
- Box: 36, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: College Forums on Current Economic Issues, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Author: The Economic and Business Foundation
  - Item 5: Trends in Industrial Relations, 1949; Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Author: California Institute of Technology
    Notes: July 21, 1949
- Box: 36, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A Strikeless Industry, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Author: M.H. Hedges
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations in the Contruction Industry, 1970; Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Author: University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign
- Box: 36, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Submission to the Government of Ontario on Matters Pertaining to Construction Labour Relations, 1969; Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Author: Ontario Federation of Construction Associations
  - Item 2: Brief Concerning the Labour Relations Act, 1970; Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Author: Metropolitan Toronto Apartment Builders Association
    Notes: October 16, 1970
- Box: 36, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labour-Management Relations in the Construction Industry in Nova Scotia, 1965; Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Author: Peter G. Green
- Box: 36, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Employers and Workers, 1956; Publication (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Author: Det Danske Selskab
  - Item 2: Dansk Arbejdsgiverforening, 1968; Publication (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Author: Diskussionsbidrag fra Arbejdsgiverside
    Notes: February 16, 1968
  - Item 3: Industrial Relations in Denmark, 1947; Publication (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Author: Socialt Tidsskrift
- Box: 36, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Dictionary of Selected Wage Terms, 1968; Publication (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Author: Trade Union Council of South Africa
    Notes: March 1968
- Box: 36, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The 1962 Directory of Speakers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Box: 36, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Labor Lessons: Notes from Europe, Publication (Box 36, Folder 12)
    Author: Arnold R. Weber
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations in Europe, 1961; Publication (Box 36, Folder 12)
    Author: Alfred B. Badger
- Box: 36, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: L'Enterprise: Exigences Economiques et Humaines, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Author: Association Nationale des Assistantes Sociales et des Assistants Sociaux
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations - France: The Present Situation and Trends in Collective Bargaining in the 70's, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Author: Management Counsellors International
- Box: 36, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Settlement of Social Conflicts in the Federal Republic of Germany, 1972; Publication (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Author: Heinz Ruhnau
    Notes: February/March 1972
  - Item 2: Das Moderne Arbeits-Recht, 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Author: Erich Sachers
    Notes: November 14, 1959
- Box: 36, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Reforming Relationships in Industry, 1971; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: Leonard F. Neal
  - Item 2: Labour Relations and Conditions of Work in Britain, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: Great Britain Central Office of Information
  - Item 3: The Labour Market, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: John Corina
  - Item 4: Labour Relations and Conditions of Work in Britain, 1967; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: A New Thinking for Industry, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: Moral Re-Armament
  - Item 6: Trade Unionists: We Can Defeat the Tory Bill!, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: The Partisan Press
  - Item 7: The Industrial Relations Bill: A Declaration of War, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: IMG
  - Item 8: Trade Unions after Donovan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: Peter McGregor
  - Item 9: Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Investing in People: The Marlow Idea, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: Alfred Badger
  - Item 11: Industrial Relations in the 1970's, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: L.F. Neal
    Notes: January 20, 1970
  - Item 12: Industrial Relations, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Participation in a Competitive Economy, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: Peter McGregor, Gordon Lishman
  - Item 14: The Donovan Report, 1968; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: O.H. Parsons
  - Item 15: The Report of the Industrial Partnership Committee Partners at Work, 1968; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Concise Guide to Industrial Relations, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: Institute of Supervisory Management
  - Item 17: Concise Guide to Industrial Relations, 1964; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: Labour Relations and Conditions of Work in Britain, 1965; Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Author: Great Britain Central Office of Information Reference Pamphlet
- Box: 36, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions and Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: An Introduction to Human Relations at Work, Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Author: John Marsh
  - Item 3: Labour Relations and Conditions of Work in Britain, 1960; Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Author: Central Office of Information
  - Item 4: A Concise Guide to Industrial Relations, 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: In Place of Strife: A Policy for Industrial Relations, 1969; Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Employment and Productivity
  - Item 6: Full Report of the Speeches, 1919; Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Author: National Industrial Conference
    Notes: February 27, 1919
  - Item 7: Labour Relations and Conditions of Work in Britain, Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Management and Men, Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Author: A.J. Allen
  - Item 9: The Public Interest, 1972; Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Author: Industrial Research and Information Services
    Notes: August 1972
  - Item 10: In Place of Strife: A Policy for Industrial Relations, 1969; Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: Fair Deal Takes Shape, 1971; Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Author: Conservative Central Office
  - Item 12: The Case Against the Government's Proposals on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Box: 36, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Economic Development and Cultural Change, Publication (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Box: 36, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employer Vulnerability Audit, Publication (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Box: 36, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations in Hospitals, 1960; Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
    Author: Hyman Parker, George Odiorne
- Box: 36, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: An Outline of a Personnel Policy for a Hotel, Publication (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Box: 36, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations, 1964; Publication (Box 36, Folder 21)
    Author: Central Board for Workers' Education
  - Item 2: On Industrial Relations; AITUC Replies to Govt. Questionnaire, 1952; Publication (Box 36, Folder 21)
    Author: All-India Trade Union Congress
- Box: 36, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A Bibliography on Labour Relations in India, Publication (Box 36, Folder 22)
    Author: P.N. Kaula
- Box: 36, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Types of Joint-Consultation and their Relations to Collective Bargaining in the Industrial Relations in Japan, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 23)
    Author: Akira Katakami
  - Item 2: The Industrial Relations System in Japan, 1900; Publication (Box 36, Folder 23)
    Author: Yoshihiro Tsurumi
- Box: 36, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: House, 1947; Publication (Box 36, Folder 24)
    Notes: March 18, 1947
  - Item 2: Massachusetts Proposals for Better Industrial Relations, 1947; Publication (Box 36, Folder 24)
    Author: The New England Council
- Box: 36, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Industrial, Agricultural, Labor Relations for Minnesota Living, 1948; Publication (Box 36, Folder 25)
    Author: Study for Community Life Problems
    Notes: January 1948
  - Item 2: The Minnesota Labor Peace Plan, 1939; Publication (Box 36, Folder 25)
    Author: Earl Christmas
    Notes: April 1939
- Box: 36, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: A Report to the President of the United States, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
    Author: U.S. Missile Sites Labor Commission
    Notes: May 26, 1962
- Box: 36, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Report on Labor Relations in the Municipal Service, 1954; Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
    Author: New York City Department of Labor
    Notes: June 9, 1954
- Box: 36, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Statutory Organisation of Industry in the Netherlands, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 28)
    Author: The Social-Economic Council
  - Item 2: Partijen en Stratigieen in Het Arbeidspolitieke Spel, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 28)
    Author: H. Buiter
- Box: 36, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Toward Better Labor-Management Relations in New England, Publication (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Box: 36, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The Nova Scotia Experiment in Labour Management Relations, 1964; Publication (Box 36, Folder 30)
    Author: C. Roy Brookbank
- Box: 36, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Report of the Select Committee on Labour Relations, 1958; Publication (Box 36, Folder 31)
    Author: Ontario Legislature
    Notes: July 10, 1958
- Box: 36, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: General Industrial Conditions and Labour Relations in Trinidad, 1954; Publication (Box 36, Folder 32)
    Author: D.W. Dalley
  - Item 2: Some Impressions Regarding German Labor Relations, 1954; Publication (Box 36, Folder 32)
    Author: William H. McPherson
  - Item 3: Labor-Management Relations: Great Britain, France, Sweden, 1951; Publication (Box 36, Folder 32)
    Notes: February 1951
- Box: 36, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Careers in Labor Relations, 1947; Publication (Box 36, Folder 33)
    Author: Florence Peterson
  - Item 2: A Career in Industrial Relations with a Glossary of Industrial Relations Terms, Publication (Box 36, Folder 33)
    Author: Arthur O. England, Harry Laurent
- Box: 36, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Freedom of Choice and the National Labor Policy, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 34)
    Author: Gerald A. Brown
    Notes: July 5, 1962
  - Item 2: Industry's Policies of Labor Relations, 1944; Publication (Box 36, Folder 34)
    Notes: May 25, 1944
  - Item 3: Industrial Relations Policy and Action, 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 34)
    Notes: October 1959
- Box: 36, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Labor Peace and Full Employment in Sweden, Publication (Box 36, Folder 35)
    Author: Institutet for Informationsmetodik
- Box: 36, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management Relations in TVA, 1949; Publication (Box 36, Folder 36)
    Notes: May 12, 1949
- Box: 36, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Relations in Switzerland, Publication (Box 36, Folder 37)
    Author: Charles Kuntschen
- Box: 36, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Remarks by T.C. De Butts, 1965; Publication (Box 36, Folder 38)
    Author: Railroad Public Relations Association
    Notes: June 14, 1965
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 36, Folder 38)
    Author: American Federation of Labor
- Box: 36, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Personnel & Labour, 1965; Publication (Box 36, Folder 39)
    Author: Japanese National Railways
- Box: 36, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Research and Social Theory, Publication (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Item 2: The Industrial Relations Inventory, Publication (Box 36, Folder 40)
    Author: Ebasco Services
  - Item 3: Human Relations in a Research Organization, Publication (Box 36, Folder 40)
    Author: National Institutes of Health
- Box: 36, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations in Ocean Shipping, 1948; Publication (Box 36, Folder 41)
    Author: Stanford University
- Box: 36, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Suggested Statistical Program Relating to Labor and Industrial Relations Activities in the Iron and Steel Industry, 1945; Publication (Box 36, Folder 42)
    Author: American Iron and Steel Institute
    Notes: May 1945
- Box: 37, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Higher Education and Labor Relations, 1946; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Author: Donald J. Shank
  - Item 2: Thirteen Years in a Labor School, 1953; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Author: Fathers Rumble & Carty
  - Item 3: The Journal of Educational Sociology, 1947; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Author: The Payne Educational Sociology Foundation
  - Item 4: Notes on the Reading Assignments, 1947; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Author: George F.F. Lombard
    Notes: 1947-1948
  - Item 5: The Teaching of Labor Relations in Engineering Schools, 1928; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Notes: November 2, 1928
  - Item 6: Students in Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The Universities and Industrial Relations, 1949; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Author: McGill University
  - Item 8: Teaching Industrial Relations by Having Students Assume the Roles of Management and Labor, Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Author: J.K. Gerdel
  - Item 9: Industrial, Agricultural Labor Relations, 1948; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Programs for Advanced Study, 1946; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Notes: January 1, 1946
- Box: 37, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Curseo de Relacoes Humanas Para O Trabalhador, 1966; Publication (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Author: Orientacao Social
- Box: 37, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor Breakthrough in the Southern Classroom, Publication (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Author: League for Industrial Democracy
  - Item 2: Agreement Between the State of New York and the Civil Service Employees Association, Inc., Publication (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Author: Institutional Services Unit
  - Item 3: Labor-Management Relations in the Secondary School Curriculum, Publication (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Author: Walter J. E. Schiebel
- Box: 37, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Western Jesuit, 1972; Publication (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Author: Jesuit Seminary Association
    Notes: Spring 1972
- Box: 37, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Progress Report 65, Publication (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Author: Suffolk Department of Labor
- Box: 37, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Labor Front in Sweden, 1946; Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Author: Naboth Hedin
  - Item 2: What Can the United States Learn from Sweden's Past Labor Pains?, 1946; Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Author: The Commercial and Financial Chronicle
  - Item 3: The Institute for Labour Studies, 1970; Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Author: Rudolf Meidner
  - Item 4: Demokrati pa Arbejdspladsen Debatten I Sverige, Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Author: Arbejdsministeriets Udvalg Vedr. Forholdene Pa Arbejdspladserne
  - Item 5: Forhallandet Lo-TCO, Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Author: Otto Nordenskiold
  - Item 6: Development of Labour Peace in Sweden, 1971; Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Author: Swedish Trade Union Confederation
- Box: 37, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Principles Behind Employer-Employee Harmony, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Readjustments for Ending Industrial Strife, 1938; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Author: Industrial Relations Association of Chicago
    Notes: February 15-17, 1938
  - Item 3: A Way of Industrial Life, 1938; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Author: Louis K. Comstock
    Notes: August 2, 1938
  - Item 4: Guiding Principles for Organized Labor and Management Relations, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Author: Council for Social Action Congregational Christian Churches
  - Item 5: A Forward Look in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: The Causes of Industrial Peace, 1947; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Management's Program for Improving Industrial Relations, 1946; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Author: Carroll E. French
    Notes: June 20, 1946
  - Item 8: If I Were an Industrial Manager, 1944; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Notes: December 6, 1944
  - Item 9: The Basic Elements of the Labor Problem, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Author: A.H. Raskin
  - Item 10: The Perils of Democracy, 1918; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Author: John H. Kirby
    Notes: February 19-20, 1918
  - Item 11: The Role of Labor in Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Author: Jack Barbash
  - Item 12: The Conditions of Labor Peace, 1946; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: The Corporation and the Union, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Author: Center for the Study of Democratic Institution
  - Item 14: Statesmanship in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: What's Ahead for Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Notes: December 1960
- Box: 37, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: State Government Labor Relations, 1945; Publication (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Box: 37, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The American Industrial Relations System in 1975, Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Author: John T. Dunlop
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Policies, 1965; Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Corporation and the Union, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The American Industrial Relations System in 1975, Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Statesmanship in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Change or Consequences: Our Industrial Relations Future, Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: The New Frontier in Labor Relations, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Author: The Personnel Journal, Inc.
- Box: 37, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: An Assembly on Employee-Management Cooperation, 1964; Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Author: Society of Personnel Administration
    Notes: February 27, 1964
  - Item 2: Focus on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Improving Human Relations, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Notes: November 1956
  - Item 4: How Labor and Management Can Keep the Government Out of Collective Bargaining, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: How Labor and Management Can Keep the Government Out of Collective Bargaining, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Employee Relations, 1984, Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Industrial Relations Policies, 1964; Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce of United States
  - Item 8: High School Debate Kit, Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Box: 37, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Les Relations Industrielles aux Etats-Unis, Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Author: Albert Verschueren
  - Item 2: Labor-Management Developments - Challenge to the Nation, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Labor Management Relations in the 1960's, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Author: Iota Rho Chi
    Notes: October 1961
  - Item 4: Labor in a Changing Society, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Author: Harold S. Roberts
  - Item 5: Labor-Management Relations: A Look Ahead, Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Author: Charles R. Sligh
  - Item 6: Labor-Management Developments - Challenge to the Nation, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Box: 37, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: New Frontiers in Employee Relations, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Author: Virgil B. Day
- Box: 37, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Two Statements on Labor/Management Relations in the 1970s, Publication (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Author: James D. Hodgson, Matthew A Kelly
  - Item 2: Unions, Management, and the Public, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Author: Yale Reports
    Notes: April 1, 1962
- Box: 37, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Special Bibliography of NAM Industrial Relations Publications, Publication (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Box: 37, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Industrial Progress and Economic Research, Publication (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Author: University of Pennsylvania
  - Item 2: Research: The Forgotten "R" in Transportation, 1963; Publication (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Author: Harry J. Bruce, Stanley Zionts
  - Item 3: Intercollegiate Bibliography; Cases in Research and Development, 1965; Publication (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Research and the Community, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Author: New York Department of Commerce
- Box: 37, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Mobilizing Manpower for Research, Publication (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Box: 37, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Materials for Research in Southern Industrial History, Publication (Box 37, Folder 17)
    Author: James F. Doster
  - Item 2: Trade Association Industrial Research, 1948; Publication (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Industrial R&D Funds in Relation to Other Economic Variables, Publication (Box 37, Folder 17)
    Author: National Science Foundation
  - Item 4: Cases in Research and Development, 1965; Publication (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Box: 37, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Merit Ratings of Liability and Workmen's Compensation Risks, 1913; Publication (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Author: Carl M. Hansen
    Notes: July 8-11, 1913
  - Item 2: Proposed Bill of the Commission to Investigate the General Subject of Industrial Accidents in the State of Idaho, 1914; Publication (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Author: State of Idaho
    Notes: May 1914
  - Item 3: Industrial Accidents, their Compensation and Prevention, 1913; Publication (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Notes: October 1, 1913
  - Item 4: A Plan for Applying Schedule Rating to Workmen's Compensation Insurance with a Tentative Draft of a Schedule for Rating Machine Shops Together with Standard Requirements and Rules and Regulations Applicable Thereto, Publication (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Author: Industrial Accident Board of California
- Box: 37, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Occupational Safety and Health Activities in the Federal Government, 1978; Publication (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Notes: June 2, 1978